Guide to the Jerry Clapsaddle papers, 1981-2005
George Mason University Libraries
- Series 2: Photographs and Slides, 1973-2002; (1 box)
  This series contains photographs and slides of art from students and museums, as well as art in public places.
  - Art in Public Places Artists, 1989 (Box 21, Folder 1)
    Slides
  - Recent Works, 1986 (Box 21, Folder 2)
  - Alan Fisher's Student Slides, 1990 (Box 21, Folder 3)
    Oakton High School
  - Art in Public Places and Art Apprenticeships, 1973 (Box 21, Folder 4)
  - Cat's Journal (Box 21, Folder 5)
    Journal, Slides, Cassette Tape
  - SF 2 Exhibition, 1999 (Box 21, Folder 6)
    Photographs
  - Carol - Issues, 1989 (Box 21, Folder 7)
    Cassette Tapes
  - Shipping Crates, 1984 (Box 21, Folder 8)
  - Virginia Commonwealth University - George Mason University Print Exchange (Box 21)
    Blue Container
  - SFI Exhibit Installation, Blue Container (Box 21)
- Series 3: Videotapes, 1995-2000; (2 boxes)
  This serious contains VHS tapes of art projects by students.
  - Art Exhibits, 1995-1996 (Box 22, Folder 1)
    Fliers, Response Gallery, Video Rental, Correspondence
  - Video Resource Catalog, October, 1997 (Box 22, Folder 2)
  - George Mason University Faculty Handbook, 2001 (Box 22, Folder 3)
  - U Street Sounds, August, 2000 (Box 23)
    GMU-TV
  - Stairwell Project, 1997 (Box 23)
  - Stairwell Project, Spring, 1997 (Box 23)
  - Steve Kim - Video Projections of Law (Box 23)
  - The Audacity of Moon Advertising (Box 23)
  - SF2 Student Videos (Box 23)
  - Julie Harrell - Ritual Project, April 2000 (Box 23)
  - I Am A Jackass (Box 23)
  - SF2 Student Video (Box 23)
  - Out of the Void - Katie Devins (Box 23)
    SF2 Student Videos
  - SF2 Student Videos - Ritual Project (Box 23)
  - SF2 Student Video (Box 23)
  - SF2 Student Video (Box 23)
  - Mary Clair - Ritual Project (Box 23)
  - The Lighting and Computer Art of Patrick Gill (Box 24)
  - Two Short Animation (Box 24)
    Students of Rosalind Kimball Moulton, "Mental Games" by Rosalind Kimball Moulton
  - Doug Basset - Of the First Generation (Box 24)
  - SF2 Student Video (Box 24)